<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Directory Service on TRISA Documentation</title><link>https://trisa.dev/gds/</link><description>Recent content in Directory Service on TRISA Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 11:21:42 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://trisa.dev/gds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Registration</title><link>https://trisa.dev/gds/registration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 09:21:59 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/gds/registration/</guid><description>To join the TRISA or TestNet networks, you must register with the TRISA Global Directory Service (GDS) or one of the jurisdiction-specific directory services. Registering with the directory service engages two workflows:
A KYV review process to ensure the network maintains trusted membership Certificate issuance for mTLS authentication in the network Coming soon: more details on the registration form, email verification, and the review process.
Certificate Issuance There are currently two mechanisms to receive mTLS certificates from the GDS when your registration has been reviewed and approved.</description></item><item><title>Sectigo</title><link>https://trisa.dev/gds/sectigo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 07:58:37 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/gds/sectigo/</guid><description>The TRISA Directory Service issues certificates using the Sectigo Certificate Authority via its IoT Portal. Because the directory service must collect public key material in order to facilitate an initial trusted handshake for mTLS, it uses the Sectigo IoT Manager API as part of the VASP registration and verification process. The github.com/trisacrypto/directory/pkg/sectigo package is a Go library for interacting with the API, implementing the endpoints and methods required by the directory service.</description></item></channel></rss>