<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Global Directory Service on TRISA Documentation</title><link>https://trisa.dev/gds/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Global Directory Service on TRISA Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 10:54:47 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://trisa.dev/gds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Using the GDS API</title><link>https://trisa.dev/gds/api/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 11:54:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/gds/api/index.html</guid><description>The TRISADirectory service, defined in the proto/trisa/gds protocol buffers, specifies how TRISA clients should interact with the directory service to facilitate peer-to-peer transfers.
This service includes four types of RPCs:
RPCs designed to support interactions with the Global Directory Service during a TRISA information transfer: Lookup and Search (Note: These are the primary Directory Service interactions.) RPCs designed to support the Directory Service registration and verification processes: Register and VerifyContact RPCs designed to supply the entity review and TRISA verification status of a given VASP: Verification RPCs designed to enable routine health check and status requests: Status (Note: these mirror the TRISAHealth service) service TRISADirectory { rpc Lookup(LookupRequest) returns (LookupReply) {} rpc Search(SearchRequest) returns (SearchReply) {} rpc Register(RegisterRequest) returns (RegisterReply) {} rpc VerifyContact(VerifyContactRequest) returns (VerifyContactReply) {} rpc Verification(VerificationRequest) returns (VerificationReply) {} rpc Status(HealthCheck) returns (ServiceState) {} }Lookup The Lookup RPC is designed to provide VASP certification information.</description></item><item><title>Accessing Members</title><link>https://trisa.dev/gds/members/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 14:02:37 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/gds/members/index.html</guid><description>The TRISAMembers service is an experimental service that provides extra, secure access to the directory service for verified TRISA members. Only members of the TRISA network (e.g. members who have been issued valid identity certificates) can access detailed directory service data about the network using this service. Note: Once validated, this service will be moved into the official TRISA specification.
The TRISAMembers Service This section describes the protocol buffers for the TRISAMembers endpoint, which can be found here.</description></item><item><title>Administration</title><link>https://trisa.dev/gds/admin/index.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 10:54:47 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/gds/admin/index.html</guid><description>The TRISA Global Directory Service is managed by administrators appointed by the TRISA board to support and vet VASPs registering to join the TRISA network. TRISA Admins have the following primary responsibilities:
Review new VASP registrations and vet them for access. Administrate the certificate authority on behalf of TRISA. Provide technical support and advice to VASPs. Manage the GDS system and TestNet. This section of the documentation is specifically focused on the workflows for TRISA admins.</description></item></channel></rss>