<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on TRISA Documentation</title><link>https://trisa.dev/</link><description>Recent content in Home on TRISA Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 07:58:37 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://trisa.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Integration Overview</title><link>https://trisa.dev/integration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 01:35:35 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/integration/</guid><description>TRISA Integration Overview Register with a TRISA Directory Service Implement the TRISA Network protocol Implement the TRISA Health protocol VASP Directory Service Registration Registration Overview Before you can integrate the TRISA protocol into your VASP software, you must register with a TRISA Directory Service (DS). The TRISA DS provides public key and TRISA remote peer connection information for registered VASPs.
Once you have registered with the TRISA DS, you will receive a KYV certificate.</description></item><item><title>TestNet</title><link>https://trisa.dev/testnet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 11:20:10 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/testnet/</guid><description>The TRISA TestNet has been established to provide a demonstration of the TRISA peer-to-peer protocol, host &amp;ldquo;robot VASP&amp;rdquo; services to facilitate TRISA integration, and is the location of the primary TRISA Directory Service that facilitates public key exchange and peer discovery.
The TRISA TestNEt is comprised of the following services:
TRISA Directory Service - a user interface to explore the TRISA Global Directory Service and register to become a TRISA member TestNet Demo - a demo site to show TRISA interactions between “robot” VASPs that run in the TestNet The TestNet also hosts three robot VASPs or rVASPs that have been implemented as a convenience for TRISA members to integrate their TRISA services.</description></item><item><title>Directory Service</title><link>https://trisa.dev/gds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 11:21:42 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/gds/</guid><description>The Global TRISA Directory Service (GDS) facilitates peer-to-peer exchanges between TRISA members as follows:
By providing discovery services for finding TRISA endpoints By issuing mTLS certificates to verify exchanges By providing certificate and KYC information for verification Interactions with a Directory Service are specified by the TRISA protocol. Currently, the TRISA organization hosts the GDS on behalf of the TRISA network. This documentation describes the TRISA implementation of the directory service and TRISA-specific interactions with it.</description></item><item><title>Contributing</title><link>https://trisa.dev/contributing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 11:34:06 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/contributing/</guid><description>TRISA is an open source project and welcomes contributions!
If you&amp;rsquo;re a developer whose organization is using (or planning to adopt) the TRISA protocol, this section is for you!
Navigating the Repository This repository contains a gRPC implementation of the TRISA protocol as described by the white paper, which leverages protocol buffers and Golang.
The proto folder contains the core RPC definitions, including:
the interVASP Messaging Standard (IVMS) message definitions, which serve as the basis for how two VASP peers should mutually describe entities involved in cryptographic transfers, including names, locations, and government identifiers.</description></item><item><title>Reference</title><link>https://trisa.dev/reference/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 15:59:09 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/reference/</guid><description>Stay tuned!</description></item></channel></rss>