<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on TRISA Documentation</title><link>https://trisa.dev/</link><description>Recent content in Home on TRISA Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 07:58:37 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://trisa.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://trisa.dev/reference/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 15:59:09 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/reference/faq/</guid><description>Stay tuned!</description></item><item><title>Robot VASPs</title><link>https://trisa.dev/testnet/rvasps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 12:50:23 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/testnet/rvasps/</guid><description>The TestNet hosts three convenience &amp;ldquo;robot VASPs&amp;rdquo; (rVASPs) services to facilitate integration and testing with the TRISA TestNet. These services are as follows:
Alice (api.alice.vaspbot.net:443): the primary integration rVASP used to trigger and receive TRISA messages. Bob (api.bob.vaspbot.net:443): a demo rVASP to view exchanges with Alice. Evil (api.evil.vaspbot.net:443): an &amp;ldquo;evil&amp;rdquo; rVASP that is not a TRISA TestNet member, used to test non-authenticated interactions. Note: the rVASPs are currently primarily configured for demos and work has begun on making them more robust for integration purposes; please check in with this documentation regularly for any changes.</description></item><item><title>Glossary</title><link>https://trisa.dev/reference/glossary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 15:59:09 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/reference/glossary/</guid><description>Originator: The initiator of a blockchain transaction and therefore also the initiator of a TRISA transfer. The &amp;ldquo;originator&amp;rdquo; can refer to the originating VASP, the originating customer of the VASP or both.
Beneficiary: The recipient of a blockchain transaction and therefore also the recipient of a TRISA transfer. The &amp;ldquo;beneficiary&amp;rdquo; can refer to the beneficiary VASP, the beneficiary customer of the VASP or both.
Local vs Remote VASP: A reference to the source of peer-to-peer traffic in an information exchange.</description></item><item><title>Sectigo</title><link>https://trisa.dev/gds/sectigo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 07:58:37 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/gds/sectigo/</guid><description>The TRISA Directory Service issues certificates using the Sectigo Certificate Authority via its IoT Portal. Because the directory service must collect public key material in order to facilitate an initial trusted handshake for mTLS, it uses the Sectigo IoT Manager API as part of the VASP registration and verification process. The github.com/trisacrypto/testnet/pkg/sectigo package is a Go library for interacting with the API, implementing the endpoints and methods required by the directory service.</description></item><item><title>License</title><link>https://trisa.dev/contributing/license/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 11:34:06 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/contributing/license/</guid><description>The MIT License
Copyright (c) 2021 TRISA https://trisa.io
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:</description></item></channel></rss>