<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on TRISA Documentation</title><link>https://trisa.dev/</link><description>Recent content in Home on TRISA Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 07:58:37 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://trisa.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://trisa.dev/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 01:35:35 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/getting-started/</guid><description>Getting Started with TRISA There are three key steps to getting started integrating TRISA into your organization&amp;rsquo;s Travel Rule solution:
Register with a TRISA Directory Service Implement the TRISA Network protocol Implement the TRISA Health protocol This page will walk through each of these three steps, providing links to other resources as necessary.
VASP Directory Service Registration Before you can integrate the TRISA protocol into your VASP software, you must register with the TRISA Global Directory Service (GDS).</description></item><item><title>Joining TRISA</title><link>https://trisa.dev/joining-trisa/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 09:15:46 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/joining-trisa/</guid><description>To join the TRISA network, you must register with the TRISA Global Directory Service (GDS).
Registering with the directory service engages two workflows:
A KYV review process to ensure the network maintains trusted membership Certificate issuance for mTLS authentication in the network Next, learn more about registration.</description></item><item><title>Secure Envelopes</title><link>https://trisa.dev/secure-envelopes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 15:36:09 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/secure-envelopes/</guid><description>The primary data structure for a TRISA exchange is the SecureEnvelope &amp;ndash; a wrapper for compliance payload data that facilitates peer-to-peer trust in compliance information exchanges. The design of TRISA secure envelopes had the following requirements:
Privacy: only the recipient of the secure envelope should be able to open the secure envelope, even outside of the context of an RPC that is secured by transport layer encryption. Non-repudiation: the secure envelope should cryptographically guarantee that the compliance payload is valid and has not been modified or tampered with since the original exchange.</description></item><item><title>Data Payloads</title><link>https://trisa.dev/data-payloads/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 14:54:48 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/data-payloads/</guid><description>A Payload contains information to be securely exchanged for Travel Rule compliance, including (1) identity details, (2) transaction information for both counterparties to uniquely identify the transaction on the chain, and (3) timestamps for use in regulatory non-repudiation. The payload is serialized and encrypted to be sent in a SecureEnvelope. Payloads are digitally signed to ensure that they have not been tampered with in transmission.
The formal definition of a Payload is described on this page and available in the form of protocol buffers in the trisa code repository.</description></item><item><title>Working with IVMS101</title><link>https://trisa.dev/ivms/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 11:25:52 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/ivms/</guid><description>IVMS101 (the interVASP Messaging Standard) is an internationally recognized standard that helps with language encodings, numeric identification systems, phonetic name pronunciations, and standardized country codes (ISO 3166). This page describes how to convert between JSON and protocol buffer formatting for IVMS101 records. For general information about IVMS, please visit intervasp.org.
Marshaling and Unmarshaling IVMS101 JSON data should be marshaled and unmarshaled using the encoding/json package to produce data mostly compatible with the ivmsvalidator.</description></item><item><title>TestNet</title><link>https://trisa.dev/testnet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 11:20:10 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/testnet/</guid><description>The TRISA TestNet has been established to provide a demonstration of the TRISA peer-to-peer protocol, host &amp;ldquo;robot VASP&amp;rdquo; services to facilitate TRISA integration, and is the location of the primary TRISA Directory Service that facilitates public key exchange and peer discovery.
The TRISA TestNet is comprised of the following services:
TRISA Directory Service - a user interface to explore the TRISA Global Directory Service and register to become a TRISA member TestNet Demo - a demo site to show TRISA interactions between “robot” VASPs that run in the TestNet The TestNet also hosts three robot VASPs or rVASPs that have been implemented as a convenience for TRISA members to integrate their TRISA services.</description></item><item><title>Directory Service</title><link>https://trisa.dev/gds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 11:21:42 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/gds/</guid><description>The TRISA organization hosts the TRISA Global Directory Service (GDS) on behalf of the TRISA network. The TRISA protocol specifies interactions with GDS. GDS facilitates peer-to-peer exchanges between TRISA members as follows:
By issuing mTLS certificates to verify exchanges By providing discovery services for finding TRISA endpoints By providing certificate and KYCV (Know Your Counterparty VASP) information for verification It is important to note that TRISA is a peer-to-peer network with no centralized authority for collecting or exchanging Travel Rule data.</description></item><item><title>Contributing</title><link>https://trisa.dev/contributing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 11:34:06 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/contributing/</guid><description>TRISA is an open source project and welcomes contributions!
If you&amp;rsquo;re a developer whose organization is using (or planning to adopt) the TRISA protocol, this section is for you!
Navigating the Repository This repository contains a gRPC implementation of the TRISA protocol as described by the white paper, which leverages protocol buffers and Golang.
The proto folder contains the core RPC definitions, including:
the interVASP Messaging Standard (IVMS) message definitions, which serve as the basis for how two VASP peers should mutually describe entities involved in cryptographic transfers, including names, locations, and government identifiers.</description></item><item><title>Reference</title><link>https://trisa.dev/reference/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 15:59:09 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/reference/</guid><description>Where to look for more information and assistance: Submit your registration to join the TRISA Network: TRISA Global Directory Service
Complete the certificate registration form: Certificate Registration
Connect with other VASPs, regulators, and engineers working on Travel Rule compliance: TRISA Slack
Learn the basics about TRISA and how it helps VASPs with Travel Rule compliance: Getting Started with TRISA Video Series
Check to see if your data is compatible with the IVMS 101-standard: IVMS 101 Validator</description></item></channel></rss>