<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TRISA Developer Documentation on TRISA Documentation</title><link>https://trisa.dev/index.html</link><description>Recent content in TRISA Developer Documentation on TRISA Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 10:14:24 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://trisa.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://trisa.dev/getting-started/index.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 01:35:35 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/getting-started/index.html</guid><description>Welcome! If you&amp;rsquo;re new to TRISA, this guide will provide a path to help get you started.
If you just want to get started as quickly as possible, consider simply using the TRISA Envoy self-hosted node. If you are a hands-on developer, you may wish to skip to the section for technical implementers. If you are an administrator or technical leader at your organization, you may wish to skip to the administrative guide.</description></item><item><title>Joining TRISA</title><link>https://trisa.dev/joining-trisa/index.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 09:15:46 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/joining-trisa/index.html</guid><description>This portion of the documentation describes how to become a TRISA member so that you can receive Identity Certificates and use them to perform secure information transfers with other VASPs.
To join the TRISA network, you must register with the TRISA Global Directory Service (GDS).
The mechanics of registration include two important workflows:
A KYV review process to ensure the network maintains trusted membership Certificate issuance for mTLS authentication in the network Next, learn more about the process of registration.</description></item><item><title>TRISA Envoy</title><link>https://trisa.dev/envoy/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 10:14:24 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/envoy/index.html</guid><description>Built to help compliance teams handle travel rule exchanges efficiently and economically, Envoy is an open source, secure, peer-to-peer messaging platform. Designed by TRISA engineers and compliance experts, Envoy offers a mechanism for Travel Rule compliance by providing IVMS101 data exchanges using the TRISA and TRP protocols.
Key Benefits Intuitive UI: Send and receive TRISA &amp;amp; TRP messages with a user-friendly interface. Efficient Administration: Simplify setup and maintenance with our admin tools.</description></item><item><title>TRISA Protocol and API</title><link>https://trisa.dev/api/index.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 15:08:52 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/api/index.html</guid><description>This section of the documentation describes the TRISA Protocol and API.
Navigating the Open Source TRISA Code The trisa repository contains a gRPC implementation of the TRISA protocol as described by the white paper, which leverages protocol buffers and Golang.
The proto folder contains the core RPC definitions, including:
the interVASP Messaging Standard (IVMS) message definitions, which serve as the basis for how two VASP peers should mutually describe entities involved in cryptographic transfers, including names, locations, and government identifiers.</description></item><item><title>Working with TRISA Data</title><link>https://trisa.dev/data/index.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 16:46:31 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/data/index.html</guid><description>This section of the documentation contains resources for developers who are working with TRISA data, such as:
IVMS101: TRISA uses the IVMS101 standard to describe participants in cryptographic transactions. Learn more in our documentation about working with IVMS101.
SecureEnvelopes: The primary data structure for a TRISA exchange is the SecureEnvelope, a wrapper for compliance payload data that facilitates peer-to-peer trust in compliance information exchanges. Learn more in our documentation about creating and parsing Secure Envelopes.</description></item><item><title>Global Directory Service</title><link>https://trisa.dev/gds/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 11:21:42 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/gds/index.html</guid><description>The TRISA organization hosts the TRISA Global Directory Service (GDS) on behalf of the TRISA network. The TRISA protocol specifies interactions with GDS. GDS facilitates peer-to-peer exchanges between TRISA members as follows:
By issuing mTLS certificates to verify exchanges By providing discovery services for finding TRISA endpoints By providing certificate and KYCV (Know Your Counterparty VASP) information for verification It is important to note that TRISA is a peer-to-peer network with no centralized authority for collecting or exchanging Travel Rule data.</description></item><item><title>Testing and Deployment</title><link>https://trisa.dev/testing/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 11:20:10 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/testing/index.html</guid><description>The TRISA TestNet has been established to provide a demonstration of the TRISA peer-to-peer protocol, host &amp;ldquo;robot VASP&amp;rdquo; services to facilitate TRISA integration, and facilitate public key exchange and peer discovery via TRISA&amp;rsquo;s Global Directory Service (GDS). The TestNet instance is designed for testing, and the registration process is streamlined in the TestNet to facilitate quick integration. The Testnet enables you to test and validate transactions that share sensitive information safely and securely.</description></item><item><title>OpenVASP/TRP Integration</title><link>https://trisa.dev/openvasp/index.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 09:15:46 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/openvasp/index.html</guid><description>The OpenVASP Association implements an open protocol for travel rule called TRP that is similar to TRISA but puts more focus on ease of information sharing and human-in-the-loop review than on verified counterparties and cryptography. TRISA and OpenVASP have worked together over the past several months to create a &amp;ldquo;bridge&amp;rdquo; that will allow partial compatibility between the two protocols. This page describes how implementers of TRISA nodes might integrate the bridge in their node to respond to TRP requests.</description></item><item><title>Reference</title><link>https://trisa.dev/reference/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 15:59:09 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/reference/index.html</guid><description>Where to look for more information and assistance: Submit your registration to join the TRISA Network: TRISA Global Directory Service
Create an account and complete the certificate registration form: Certificate Registration
Connect with other VASPs, regulators, and engineers working on Travel Rule compliance: TRISA Slack
Learn the basics about TRISA and how it helps VASPs with Travel Rule compliance: Getting Started with TRISA Video Series
Check to see if your data is compatible with the IVMS 101-standard: IVMS 101 Validator</description></item></channel></rss>