<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on TRISA Documentation</title><link>https://trisa.dev/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on TRISA Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 01:35:35 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://trisa.dev/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TRISA Protocol</title><link>https://trisa.dev/getting-started/protocol/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 15:08:52 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/getting-started/protocol/</guid><description>The TRISA protocol enables peer-to-peer exchange of compliance information over a mutually authenticated connection so that the identity of both the sender and the recipient can be verified. The protocol contains methods for unary and streaming information exchanges as well as helper functions for key exchange and address confirmation to facilitate the secure transfer of PII information. The protocol itself is designed to be flexible, adaptable to regulatory changes, the needs of different types of VASPs, and future proofing for tomorrow’s technology.</description></item><item><title>TRISA API</title><link>https://trisa.dev/getting-started/api/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 19:53:56 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/getting-started/api/</guid><description>The TRISA Network Protocol implementation exposes several RPCs needed to build TRISA into your organization&amp;rsquo;s application, which are defined within the protocol buffers. All TRISA members must implement both services described by the TRISA protocol (the TRISANetwork service and the TRISAHealth service) to ensure that exchanges are conducted correctly and securely.
The protocol buffers can be compiled into the language of your choice. This section describes the protocol buffers for the TRISANetwork endpoint and the protocol buffer API in Go.</description></item><item><title>TRISA Errors and Rejections</title><link>https://trisa.dev/getting-started/errors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 16:45:58 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/getting-started/errors/</guid><description>Error codes are standardized in the TRISA network to prevent confusion and allow easy identification of rejections or other problems to expedite the repair of the connection or information exchange. Then, the human-readable message stating the reason for the error should be loggable and actionable. Both standardized and unique/detail messages are acceptable. The message that caused the error should be retried with a fix, otherwise the rejection is permanent, and the request should not be retried.</description></item></channel></rss>