<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Configuration on TRISA Documentation</title><link>https://trisa.dev/gds/admin/configuration/</link><description>Recent content in Configuration on TRISA Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 18:09:44 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://trisa.dev/gds/admin/configuration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GDS</title><link>https://trisa.dev/gds/admin/configuration/gds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 18:25:10 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/gds/admin/configuration/gds/</guid><description>The GDS is a collection of three APIs and several background services backed by a global TrtlDB data store. A single GDS node implements the TRISA Directory gRPC API, the secure TRISA Members gRPC API, and the Admin REST API that powers the Admin UI. It also runs the CertMan process that issues and collects certificates from Sectigo. Its environment variables are all prefixed with the GDS_ tag. The primary configuration is as follows:</description></item><item><title>BFF</title><link>https://trisa.dev/gds/admin/configuration/bff/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 11:52:54 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/gds/admin/configuration/bff/</guid><description>The BFF (backend for frontend) is the backend API that powers the GDS UI at vaspdirectory.net. The GDS UI is intended to give users a single access portal to both the MainNet and TestNet as well as to support non-GDS features like collaborators and TRISA Service Providers. Because of this it sits in the middle of multiple services, including both the MainNet and TestNet GDS services and multiple data sources. Its environment variables are all prefixed with the GDS_BFF_ tag.</description></item><item><title>User Interfaces</title><link>https://trisa.dev/gds/admin/configuration/ui/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 14:04:26 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/gds/admin/configuration/ui/</guid><description>The GDS user interfaces that power our user and administrative web applications are built and deployed using React and webpack. Because webpack compiles the app into a bundle of HTML, JavaScript, and CSS &amp;ndash; any configuration must be available at build time (e.g. when containers are compiled). This makes configuring our React apps and user interfaces slightly more complicated.
Right now, we use a continuous integration and deployment service to build our containers (e.</description></item><item><title>TrtlDB</title><link>https://trisa.dev/gds/admin/configuration/trtl/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 12:34:23 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/gds/admin/configuration/trtl/</guid><description>TrtlDb is a globally replicated key-value store that uses anti-entropy for eventually consistent replication that minimizes egress costs, maximizes availability, and is partition tolerant. It exposes unary and streaming APIs for data access and is secured via mTLS connections. Its environment variables are prefixed with the TRTL_ tag. The primary configuration is as follows:
EnvVar Type Default Description TRTL_MAINTENANCE bool false Sets the server to maintenance mode, which will respond to requests with Unavailable except for status requests.</description></item></channel></rss>