<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Joining TRISA on TRISA Documentation</title><link>https://trisa.dev/joining-trisa/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Joining TRISA on TRISA Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 14:30:51 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://trisa.dev/joining-trisa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Registration</title><link>https://trisa.dev/joining-trisa/registration/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 09:21:59 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/joining-trisa/registration/index.html</guid><description>Before you can integrate the TRISA protocol into your VASP software, you must register with the TRISA Global Directory Service (GDS).
The TRISA Global Directory Service (GDS) provides public key and TRISA remote peer connection information for registered VASPs. For more detailed information about the directory, see the documentation on the GDS.
Once you have registered and been verified, you will receive Identity Certificates. The public key in these certificates will be made available to other VASPs via the GDS.</description></item><item><title>TRIXO Form</title><link>https://trisa.dev/joining-trisa/trixo/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 09:15:46 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/joining-trisa/trixo/index.html</guid><description>The purpose of the TRIXO questionnaire is to provide responses to a common set of questions VASPs might ask each other before exchanging Travel Rule information.
When registering for TRISA membership, applicants must submit their TRIXO questionnaire in JSON form (shown below) as part of their application. After a VASP has been issued certificates, these TRIXO details are logged in the TRISA Global Directory Service to facilitate member lookups and mutual verification ahead of information exchanges.</description></item><item><title>Anatomy of a PKCS12 file</title><link>https://trisa.dev/joining-trisa/pkcs12/index.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 09:15:46 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/joining-trisa/pkcs12/index.html</guid><description>When your registration has been reviewed and approved, you will receive mTLS certificates from the Global Directory Service (GDS). These will be sent via an email containing PKCS12 password protected certificates.
What to expect after registration and during certificate issuance:
If the registration form is valid: GDS will return a PKCS12 password. This is the password you will use to decrypt your certificates. Note This is the only time the PKCS12 password is made available during the certificate issuance process.</description></item><item><title>Certificate Authority</title><link>https://trisa.dev/joining-trisa/ca/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 07:58:37 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/joining-trisa/ca/index.html</guid><description>TRISA is unique amongst open source Travel Rule protocols in that it is a trusted network, meaning that all communications are protected. TRISA uses mTLS (mutual transport layer security) to protect communications between peers. In addition to helping protect against malicious API requests, mTLS can prevent spoofing and phishing, as well as brute force and on-path attacks.
mTLS requires that both peers in an interaction have Identity Certificates with a mutually-recognized root Certificate Authority (CA).</description></item><item><title>Domain Verification</title><link>https://trisa.dev/joining-trisa/verification/index.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 14:30:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/joining-trisa/verification/index.html</guid><description>The TRISA Certificate Authority issues x509 certificates for mTLS authentication in its peer-to-peer network. These certificates are dependent on the verified ownership of a domain name that is used both in the common name of the certificate (CN) as well as the subject alternative name (SAN) extension of the certificate. Your TRISA node must be hosted at a domain name that is in the SAN field of the certificate otherwise mTLS connections will fail.</description></item></channel></rss>