<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Administration on TRISA Documentation</title><link>https://trisa.dev/gds/admin/</link><description>Recent content in Administration on TRISA Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 10:54:47 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://trisa.dev/gds/admin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configuration</title><link>https://trisa.dev/gds/admin/configuration/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 18:09:44 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/gds/admin/configuration/</guid><description>TRISA GDS and TestNet services are primarily configured using environment variables and will respect dotenv files in the current working directory. The canonical reference of the configuration for a GDS service is the config package of that service (described below). This documentation enumerates the most important configuration variables, their default values, and any hints or warnings about how to use them.
Required Configuration
If a configuration parameter does not have a default value that means it is required and must be specified by the user!</description></item><item><title>Deployment</title><link>https://trisa.dev/gds/admin/deployment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 11:14:19 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://trisa.dev/gds/admin/deployment/</guid><description>TRISA currently maintains two side-by-side networks that are deployed in Kubernetes clusters in North America, Germany, and Singapore. The &amp;ldquo;MainNet&amp;rdquo; (also referred to as the TRISA network) is the production TRISA service where peers exchange compliance information for real transactions. The &amp;ldquo;TestNet&amp;rdquo; is a mirror network that is setup to allow peers to develop their TRISA nodes and to ensure that they are configured correctly before engaging in production transactions. For more on using the TestNet, please see the Testing documentation.</description></item></channel></rss>